(Sheldon:)Under the terms of my roommate
agreement I've had control...
(Sheldon:)...of the thermostat
ever since the sweaty night of '06.
(Howard:)Okay, you were right about Wolverine
and bone claws...
(Howard:)...but you're wrong about the cricket.
(Sheldon:)Howard, don't embarrass yourself.
The science chirps for itself.
(Sheldon:)Humorous word play.
(Howard:)No, no. Not this time.
I know insects, my friend.
(Howard:)I spent many childhood years capturing
them with nets, putting them in jars...
(Howard:)...sticking pins through them, mounting
them on cardboard with labels...
(Howard:)...identifying the genus and species.
(Howard:)In Latin.
(Raj:)Oh. Dude, you are never getting
a shiksa goddess.
(Sheldon:)That is a snowy tree cricket.
Oecanthus fultoni.
(Sheldon:)I was done with Latin by fifth grade.
(Howard:)Okay. Tell you what.
(Howard:)I am willing to bet anything
that's an ordinary field cricket.
(Sheldon:)-I can't take your money.
-What's the matter, you chicken?